the silence think it's empty space think a quiet life means a fragile place no crowd around no
noise no show so they assume there's nowhere else to go they lean back start cutting corners slow
No scenes, no warning signs, just a shift you miss between the lines
You thought it bent, you thought it stayed, but it was measuring the price you paid
just to feel alive don't need a crowd just to survive
How are you doing?
I'm okay, how are you doing?
I'm good, I'm good.
I thought I would pop in real quick and say hi
since I caught ya on here.
Yeah, there was a live last night the guy that's you know doing the door knocks was a featured guest
I'm celebrated guest actually. Oh go more IRL on him and you're doing good work. Keep up the good work to him
You know
Kind of wait somebody knocked on your door and said that no this is what they were saying in Kate's
But it's the guy that's doing it Tony the guy. Yeah, he was he was like the featured guest on there on the show
I guess and they're all celebrating that behavior that illegal behavior
also
I know that I know that they're celebrating it elsewhere, which I've seen the messages and things like that
You know what goes around comes around. I know it
Sometimes feels like it never will but I've seen it happen enough time. So I do believe that
Are you reporting all this to you know, your police or whoever?
Okay, good
And yeah, it makes it easier with, you know,
when I extract the transcripts or have them, you know,
I have it transcribed and have it analyzed.
And it's like, you know, you can see like what happened,
like what they were saying, like yesterday was,
I have a little bit of like an analysis of it.
It was mentions on the show and it says,
there's things said like, I'll put a gun to your skull.
I could kill you and get away with it.
I know where you live.
Okay, yeah, yeah, this is and then this is let me see what else okay, so and then Tony's saying this Kate
And if he mentions of Tony Tony joins the panel says he supports the boycott against psyches kids
Psyche is feeling it lately predicts the future real crash out says he's personally contributed pressure against you
refers to his activity as doing my thug my thug diesel the coast encouraged him and places his hard work
The docks are gonna have a keep a knock in
This sounds like a reference to doxing or harassment pressure campaigns,
contextually, it's framed as intimidation theater.
Tony discusses being doxed by Psyche, but says the information was outdated.
It's kind of a failed dox because they don't live anywhere near that anymore.
Another panelist asks Tony, what's his hard work?
Host explains Tony is ding dong, gitching, pressing and holding people accountable.
That framing suggests Tony's reputation in the group of revolves around
harassment style, trolling activism against targets they dislike.
Tony leaves panel after reaffirming support.
I'm dedicated to the cause.
And so, yeah, it's like a Berkeley signaling,
public loyalty signaling, prediction of my downfall,
talking about the boycott and things like this.
But, you know, I did have 80 people in the chat
the other day.
Now that term ding dong, who specifically is saying that?
I think that that's what Kate explained Tony's,
what Tony's doing and then he was too, you know.
And it's like many comments depend on monitoring my live streams, my panels, my mods, my audience
size, my reactions, and my relationships, and it's like psychisexually harassed straight
men on here nonstop.
We claim that Alex McQueen and ghosts don't fuck with psyche anymore and I lost my major supporters
Mockery that viewers will miss my AI videos. My AI content becomes recurring punchline throughout the stream
They openly support a boycott against me and encourage and continue pressure social isolation
important because this becomes coordinated group reinforcement rather than isolated criticism and
E-begging suicide baiting trick situation Benny situation and Brandon Q supporter
the reasons for the boycott so okay well first and foremost the boycott evidently did not work
because i don't know what happened last night but the night before when i was on your panel
you had over 70 viewers okay now man you know the reason i was asking about that term ding dong
made her reemergent.
She uses that phrase frequently
so that could be stemming from her camp.
I mean, look, there's some things going on, okay?
I've received threats ever since I made it known
that some of these people who are parents
who are fraudulently labeling people PDFs and whatnot,
if they accept donations from anyone,
who is labeled that, that's an open door for CPS or DCF to investigate them.
There's people pretty upset that I put that information out there, but that's the reality.
So it's a double-edged sword. I mean, people can keep doing whatever they want to do,
but they're really just drawing a lot of attention to themselves. In the end,
you're just going to win because even when you have the hate, it just draws attention to you.
Yeah
Exactly well like that video that you have seven laws of power or laws of power
People look at results. They don't necessarily look at
The you know the past. Oh, yeah, you just keep
trucking, keep moving forward.
Yeah, because I have, I've had ups and downs
and like there was like 40 people yesterday,
but no one was talking.
I think people are intimidated a little bit.
There's, you know, the Arthur going,
oh, congratulations Q, Q is running the, the psyche boycott.
You know, like Q is now the moral authority, you know,
jumping onto this bandwagon with this, the boycott.
He thinks that he's smarter than he is.
And,
It is already backfiring on him.
I mean, I wouldn't say that his life is exactly stellar.
I wouldn't say that he's in the best position at all.
Yeah.
So...
I hear you get fired or something like that from his job and...
Um, yeah, so I I don't I don't know. Um, but yeah, he's a man. I mean, he's admitted to assaulting women and and
We know he he maced that homeless
Where do you go from here at this point in your life when you're you know, if I were in his like let's say that
I could put my brain in his body. I would think to myself
Screw all this internet stuff
Let me try to get myself enrolled in college. Let me try to get a scholarship
Let me try to do something to get a degree because see a guy like that
He's not thinking long-term. He's thinking okay. I'm gonna be in my 20s forever. Man those years go by fast and
Looks fade right
Because he went to the library and met some guy at the library that moved him in right away
Um, and so we haven't had to be moved in with, but you know, who knows what the arrangement
is because he's been living there rent free.
Oh, I think we know what the arrangement is, but, um, I, I, I, all I'm going to say is
that I've seen it over and over again to where men and women, you know, they start off doing
things that they shouldn't be doing when they're in their twenties, early thirties.
She was flying high for a lot of years and now she's pushing 40, living in her car, making a fool of herself, opportunities lost, and you never get that time back.
Same goes for, you know, it's when you're young, it's one thing, but if you don't switch up the game and plan for your future, when you get older.
I wouldn't be surprised if he's moving to Oklahoma soon, you know, I think he might I
You know, I was surprised that he was
You know turning his nose up at that option
Really? Yeah, because he does not have many options at all. You know, he can speak as
pseudo confidently as he wants
But I see through it
Most people with a brain do
Yeah
Well 300 glow 300 glow you're gonna marry a rich man, so you're gonna go gay for pay
Okay, well, that's an option for I guess a lot of the a lot of these panel burst guy
I guess their only option is to to marry a guy at this point, you know, it's like
I would want to marry if I want to get in a business contract with a guy at sort of business basically
You know, I used to know somebody who said that they think that polygamous marriage should be legal
Just like you know, you could have multiple owners of a business
You should have multiple parties willing to enter a marital contract because actually it would be um
financially beneficial to the people involved.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But with all these black widows in the community,
like, you know, I'd be kind of afraid to marry anybody
who are black, black, you know.
Yeah, they might be looking for, you know,
I'm convinced that there's a few who look for candidates
that they can get insurance policies on,
especially the,
Extreme substance abusers, you know, what a better way to enrich yourself find an extreme substance abuser getting insurance policy on them move them in create a situation to where they O. D.
Yeah, I think we've seen that actually happen, but a few people say anything about it
I don't know if you knew who KZ was but KZ just recently passed away and he gets he got
Remember the screen name, but I didn't know that they passed away. Yeah, he got arrested for I think a assault to a police officer or something and then
Either her here. I mean our G had the obituary, but I hear he was either stabbed in in jail or he had some I got alcohol withdrawal
in there or something like that, but you know, he was always around, but yeah, he was
going through hard times, but
He had that a salt charge spitting on a pregnant woman, you know years ago
And that was very controversial of people that I never cared for him on the show really but
But you know accused him the same thing spitting on a woman and
urinating on the public bench and then assaulting assaulting people, but now he's the moral authority. I guess in the community and
Interesting. He's just a big mouth and most people in these communities are followers
Yeah, that's the sad part about it, too. It's like, you know
There's a lot of followers, but it's like, I also, like I said, the trash took itself out because there's a lot of people that were just like monopolizing the show, and I would always let people up, you know, you know, RG, always let up, and Arthur, and now they're all in this boycott and badmouthing me and praising Q, and Bita says Sandman actually started the boycott by kicking me off his show.
you know, without getting paid to do it, you know, and so she she's so proud of her her man, you know, she's she's
Yeah, I'm surprised that some of the people actually I'm surprised at RG because you basically put him on the map
I'm so who else who else is aligning themselves with this?
well, Kate, Kate, and Kate, Tony, um like Arthur
beta
Also, like, there's some, like, you know, I went into what's her name and she is that
IP2 person with the high voice, you know, I think she had a controversy soon, but I
mean, if I go into any chat, like, I was welcome in her chat, but then I start getting doxxed
and I went to Q's chat, I started getting doxxed and I'm sorry, I mean, blogger's chat,
blogger, I started getting doxxed in his chat, he didn't do anything about it, you know,
Um, I had to block out certain certain words and stuff in my because that's all they tried to do well
None of these people matter. I mean, do you notice that for the most part the people that you're naming?
They never leave their live streams up. They can barely maintain
Good standing with their channels
They're all kind of fly by night like when they're streaming that people might notice them
But when they're not streaming no one dies you have staying power
Yeah, and that's all you really need to
keep in mind
Yeah, I'm hanging in there and
You know, it's not always easy in this community
But it's like I'm all hanging there and now they're saying there
Well, they're saying that it was impossible that I had 80 people in the other night
So I must have been bought it and oh, they're gonna start botting me
So I can get my hopes up and they're trying to trigger me and hoping I crash out and all the stuff and it's like well
I'm fine. I'm enjoying my chat still. They'll come crawling back. Yeah. They always do. Yeah. I got a new vape. It's pretty cool. Oh, good for you. What is there like a flavor to it or? It says blue dream. Blue dream. And so, you know, these are kind of. Is it nicotine or cannabis or what is it? Yeah, they're cannabis. Okay. I'm in this.
This box, it took me a while to figure out how to turn it on,
but yeah, it's a little vape,
but I think it tells you the heat of it.
How much is remaining and how many seconds it takes it is kind of strong for me. It's so I have to be very
They're too strong for me. I I've tried the vapes before they're they're too much for me and
I'm actually like like really trying to keep my body really really, you know, just clean of everything right now
It kind of sucks because it's so I'm like beyond
I'm on the other side of sober from being sober, okay
I'll still have some wine or something on occasion, but I'm substantially, substantially,
substantially limiting myself when it comes to that. You know, I'm really getting into
learning about the Christian Kabbalah now. Okay, cool.
Yeah you turned you turned me on to learning about a few things because the other night when
we spoke before you went to sleep you were showing your medallion and then you were showing me the
various letters on it and then the opposite side of it and I started you know I did a whole live
about it so I'm going to do that exploration into Christian Kabbalah in tandem with my Christian
offline more so. It's just for my own personal knowledge base.
Well, I read really good, I had these Bibles, I still have one of them like Leviticus or something like that, but it's like, it was like, it was going through the first five books of the Bible, which is like called the Torah, but it was kind of explaining it cabalistically and
Counter parts that are the 72 demons. I find that absolutely fascinating. Yeah, so I'm I'm learning about that right now
And I'm having fun with it because I didn't know and I've always loved
the concept of angels a
lot, I love
Anything to do with angels. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I mean it's like they're powerful archetypes of like God's will or like, you know his
Helpers, you know that he sometimes will send for people and a lot of people have had stories
I think you might have had a story like you know
These people that just showed up at the right place the right time the scooter accident
You know a lot of people like to show the crash of the accident because you know it is comical
I can laugh at myself, but people hardly ever show
that man who appeared who helped me and he really came out of nowhere and he looked he was so
attractive you know I don't know if my head was a little like out of sorts that I thought that or what
But I think that was an angel, or at least that was somebody
embodying an angelic spirit at that moment,
because he made sure I was OK.
I know he was talking to me basically
to make sure I didn't have a concussion.
Such a nice guy.
And he just came out of nowhere.
It was so strange.
There was nobody around that day.
I have the video footage of that over on my IP2 wiki info channel, but
Yeah, I've had a few occurrences to where I think back and I'm like was that an angel and I kind of think so maybe I've been very
Blust in a lot of ways when I think about it
Yeah, and there are definitely earth angels and
Even special humans, you know, I think with that angelic
Light or you know that that can sometimes appear for you know, you know, just mysteriously and
Disappear just as fast
Angels in human form. Yeah, so
I'm focusing on the positive sides, you know, oh, yeah, and then the 72 demons too is like, you know, those are
I made an AI song.
Actually, I'm not sure which one to pick.
I made an AI song of the 72 angels' names.
And then I'm gonna make a video to go,
well, I wanna memorize all the names.
That's how I'm gonna do it. You kind of gave me that tip. Yeah, because they're all um, actually in the way that they
Calculated that too. I guess it's like something that there's like a passage in the Bible with Moses and they take every like third letter
Yes, there's together. Do you see how they yes every every angel has a three-letter name and
What's fascinating one of my favorite biblical stories is when Moses parts the Red Sea
Do you realize that he utilized those names to do it?
Yeah, that's that's the connection between the Kabbalah and the Christian Bible is
When Moses parted that sea he was using
um the 72 angels names so somehow like I wonder does it have to do with the vibrational frequency
of speaking the names does it have to do with him calling the angels down and they came down
they were like all right we're gonna part this sea and get y'all out of here I mean that's I
wish I could be a time traveler and just see that because so many things technologically
explain certain miracles in the Bible or in other religious texts, but we cannot part water. We cannot
part major bodies of water. That's a mystery. And I mean, imagine witnessing that, man.
Well, there's stories in Tibet about how they were able to move a lot of like rocks and things
like that. They're actually by their voice. And they think they even said the pyramid.
Yeah, sound you sound and it would like lift these huge boulders into the air and there's like
Archaeologically or like, you know things that they've made that is like how did they there's no idea how they how they could have made such a thing
You know without like a technology and without like, you know, like equipment and you know construction equipment and
They and these these monasteries and things are still standing in Tibet
you know, the Tibet got kind of emptied out of all the Lamas, you know, by the Chinese government and stuff.
But I mean a lot of them like fled to India and then all then actually all over the all over the earth
They started like ashrams and things like that to start teaching and so that's how they a lot of the Lamas came to America
As well to start teaching just like that's how kind of also yoga came in by yoga nanda
you know, I think he was like sponsored by the Rothschild or something like that to come
to America and start teaching yoga. There's interesting stories in the backgrounds.
You remember that live, there was a hard, oh yeah, so I read out in Nancy saw that live,
I guess. Yeah, yeah, I'm lucky that I didn't have any bone sprake or anything. The only thing
Chipped a little bit, but it was such a small chip because I did get
Myself scanned I went to the doctor just to make sure and
There was no reason for them to go in they were like that's just gonna dissolve into your body. You're fine
That's like good, but um
I've been very lucky health and medically throughout my life when I think about it. I've never broken a bone
I think you said the same thing. Yeah
I've never had any major injuries ever.
So it's a good thing I was wearing my helmet that day,
you know, but I still have that scooter.
And I still do go out on my little scooter rides
on occasion, I got over my fear of that.
So I went out recently a few days ago, actually.
Yeah, I got my bike still a little bit.
I just got to get a part and I can fix my bike.
because the lock I had got all tangled into it and I finally had the lock taken out and
it just required one small part so um I can get that fixed and I'll be out of my bike again so
I'll have a yay yeah that'll be good um I went to the pier yesterday got a fish taco
on Fridays at the pier it's like five dollars I saw some of the live yeah
It was fun with easy and yeah, just good to get out of the house and walk around then
But then he told me about this cut water. He's like these and they're very strong
It's like 12.5% alcohol or a small can
I had a long island cut water. Yeah, cut water. It's like I have one right here. Okay. This is the strawberry margarita one
Okay, hold on. Yeah, they're cut water cut water. Okay
Yeah, and it's, well, this one's 10% alcohol,
but the Long Island iced tea and the other one
were like 12.5%, so pretty strong.
Yeah, that is pretty strong.
Then I fell asleep and then I got the vapes
and then I was right back to sleep
and so, because these knocked me out for a little while.
So you're just kind of chilling and relaxing, right?
Yeah, kind of relaxing weekend, you know?
And it's like, yeah.
All you're gonna get together with family tomorrow
and stuff for,
You know the holiday. Yes
Yeah, and and tomorrow you have a show too, right?
Yeah, I do what time was it 2 p.m. Okay?
Okay, great. I'll be able to watch that. So everyone that's gonna be on your IPT wiki channel or the no
IRL news time IRL news time. Yeah, so that should go pretty well. It'll be brief
It'll be well might not be brief. It depends on what he wants to talk about really
Yeah, you know, there's a set topic, but then I said that we could diverge if we want it to
So we'll see how that goes
Look forward to that tomorrow. I'm gonna definitely be tuning in
Yeah, just the more I see and you know now beat is going after crystalline. I know and
Bro prefer to decline her cat and she's calling her oh well cuz you know beat it in the snow
Now people are bringing up this young cheeto who I guess be that apparently took a bubble bath with this 19 year old
You know not like why I never heard that rumor. Yeah, does anybody know more about it?
Like I just remember her like, you know, she went so all this is such a long time ago now when I think about it
It really is and
You know
What Bita is going to have to learn is that you do have to be able to take what you dish out, but when it comes to CA.
Yeah, she feeds off the altercations. Okay, that's why I decided I'm not engaging with her. Nope
I will not go on her panel
I will not hardly acknowledge her really. Yeah, but
And I'm definitely not team beta
But between the two if I had to like save the life of one of them it would be beta. Okay
Beta if I were her
would not engage or interact or anything because look I know we all have our
issues and whatnot but when it comes to CA she only is able to survive because
she has people who do take care of her she's not functional really and what she
does online eventually
Some she's gonna mess with the wrong person who brings some legalities upon her
That's what's gonna happen with her. She already got a straight. Yeah. Yes. She did. Didn't she?
Yeah, she's on her backup channel or something and yeah, and that's a form of um
What is it called TOS evasion sure is yeah
Well, and you know she yeah, I mean I don't I mean I'm banned from her panel or chat and then I guess
The ban from beat is and views chat and panel now
So it's like, you know, basically all they can try to do is silence me at this point
and like well they have nothing to say I mean look you actually I'm so glad that you're getting
now the house and you know showing whatever's in your neighborhood and whatnot that's solid
IRL I feel like if you're gonna be in the game you need to not just
Talk the talk, but you need to walk the walk. So you're becoming a multifaceted streamer panel host commentator
You have your original content. You have the artistry. You're going out doing IRL
That makes you a well-rounded solid streamer the people who are really causing the problems. You don't see them going outside
You don't see them creating anything original all they do
is create problems to create this endless back and forth which is pointless in really very low value.
Yeah, that's a very good assessment. That's perfect assessment actually of what's going on because it's like that's there's I mean
There's about starting conflict and having continuing drama
And so whatever they have to jump on though, even like now it's now it's all she has to say about me
It's like well, he lets his cats out to catch and they catch mice and that's like her big complaint about how
Well, I thought cats have had have they never seen Tom and Jerry that
Cats chase mice that's like
their life purpose to go after little creatures and they actually keep the populations of the
creatures that are pests to us down. I'm happy about the cats.
Yep, I know and so yeah, I think it's like this like cats are gonna cat like I mean unless they're like locked up inside
I know some people have like, you know, they're not able to let the cat outside
They don't they have a balcony and stuff like that and the cats are more indoor
But are the elites cats going on the balcony then like I guess like you know and then Crystal Anne
I guess had declawed her cats and be the
Oh, that's horrible. Like, you know, you shouldn't do that because what if the cat gets out? It needs to be able to defend itself
right and
Yeah, and that also like it disorients the cats a little is that legal to do that
Not in California, but in some in some in some places it is like, you know, Oklahoma probably it's legal
But here it's a big no-no in California, like, you know, even how it's wrong
I mean, you know like imagines like what if humans could be pets and
You know, whatever made us
their pets decided okay we're going to take off their hands and feet to where they can't really
go out anywhere and function can you imagine like if your hands were surgically removed or your feet
oh my god i don't even want that could be a horror movie like aliens come in and make us pets oh god
yeah oh yeah aliens is pet I mean how many people as pets yeah there's a whole south part about
The reality show, and then it was going to be canceled and stuff like that.
It was just an alien reality show called Earth.
I think we are.
Well, that's why they created this streaming for us.
They do, I think that someone out there is watching us all the time.
Yeah, it's great. It's great surveillance if you think about it, like the people pulling
asleep, even like, you know, maybe tell you secrets in their sleep and stuff, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. It's crazy to think about.
Yeah, but also that she makes his AI like and she's like, you know, she complains about my AI
But Kate made this AI of like and she makes like, you know, she has to make my house dirtier than it
My house is like you you can probably find a good picture where it's like kind of you know
I'm seeing there's so many things that people see she's not worth the time in my opinion because she's you know
Unknown she wants the interaction because she wants more people to know about her but
there's a lot of things people could make AI in regards to her and she would cry
oh I know she would cry. That's why I held off because I feel like ooh I could be
so mean and it's like I just said all I did was like you know I made a shrek
and there was actual shrek and stuff but she made me as the donkey in shrek so
and she put it her as this beautiful
Beautiful. She's not beautiful at all. I don't know if you've actually her AI of herself is very flattering
Yeah, yeah
She did she basically use that picture pin and put that one as a green, you know, and it made me as it's like
Don't donkey dripping and looks like some kind of like ectoplasm or something like that like the
Distressed look on my face. I don't know. I think I think some people are helping her out though. It's like probably
She has some but I don't know if she can use it that well, but or I guess she'd maybe just use this chat to beat you for it
but
Don't know. She should certainly has criticism shut up idiots show floor. Yeah, they never show their floor
Do they didn't they never show their own places or you know, would they like to
Magnify things today when I was walking I had the phone kind of close to my face
I guess but there's like, you know, someone put an eight or someone put a picture up
Says look he's balding. He's bald and it's a you know looks like I'm like a hundred years old in the picture
It's like I'm smiling, you know, no, you don't you actually
I don't know what you're doing, but you're actually looking healthier over the past month or so in my opinion. Thank you
You've also gained some weight not not to say that you have to or need to but I'm just saying you are
Looking a little bit different lately. Yeah, I don't know. Maybe it's cuz we're getting to the summertime. I don't know
How do you go?
I got to my beach party ready, you know?
So, I know you're ready.
Well, hey, Baywatch time.
I don't know.
I got to do some stuff too.
Actually, I'm thinking that over the next,
well, starting Monday,
I'm starting a certain kind of fast.
So I do kind of want to share that as I'm doing it.
That way I stick to it.
Cause I feel like if I share it,
You know need to stick to it. Yeah, but I'll only be eating
basically salads starting next week and
I'm gonna be streaming a lot next week most likely God willing I will be
There's also like it's like all the master clad and so I guess it's like honey and
lemon juice inside like, and then you drink that too,
like during the time and that's supposed to be.
Oh, I can't do just the liquid fast.
Like it's too hungry.
Oh, I get hungry.
Yeah.
But it's like, it's the beverage though,
like maybe, because that's supposed to be cleansed,
like a really cleansing thing.
I just know Robin Quivers was on it and she lost
so much of weight.
I think she lost a lot.
I love her.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've been watched Howard in a long time though, like so I don't know what's really I just I'd last time
I saw it he was it was turned into like he still does he have a show that's still going
I think it was can't think it might have been canceled, but he was like the last time I saw him he was like
Doing like he was at home, you know, and like he was kind of like he got he was kind of jealous of the live streamers
He was like I went to broadcasting school and now everyone has a show
Oh a lot of people I mean it really is kind of
It would piss certain mainstream people off the way that live streaming and the internet has made it so easy
for what used to be something that
You had to really work in order to get a show on the radio or you had to have the connections
You know to be a you know, even a on a reality show now you can just make your own reality show, but
You know, there's there's new things coming to where
You know, it does take work to really achieve a level of success. Yeah
And I'm gonna keep going and I do believe I could have success and you know even get a but you are you have reached a level of
Success now it's just more success
Yeah, because I guess like I gamble was saying oh my god
You know people make just you make just pennies on YouTube and like you know and I've made over a thousand dollars in a month
Do you look he?
Let me tell you something interesting I discovered.
You know, I just did a, recently I did a Google search on him.
I just typed in Ganvel, right?
And he came up as a public figure, but labeled as a singer.
So I immediately did send a correction into Google
in regards to that.
But see, here's, and I've seen people do this before.
He actually doesn't have any artistic talent.
He's a big mouth. He's a good talker. He peaked early when it comes to his intellect.
When he was younger, it was like, oh, he's a novelty. He's special. But...
He's just an asshole as he's getting older and I've said this and I know that considering a few things that he said
It impacted him my saying that because it's the truth
But he did he's never been in the music industry. He's not a singer
I think that people have mislabeled him that in databases because of the Aaron Carter thing
And here's my question if he had never been entertained by Aaron would Aaron still be alive?
Right Aaron had never entertained crystal in a lot of these other people would he still be alive if
I were either of them
That's that's quite a thing to
Shoulder
When I think about it
Yeah
I think that things are not going to work out as certain people think well
I mean it's like I know like he was just like you know trying to label himself as this predator hunter or PDF hunter
And then it's like it was just like Brandon and Zea was like only top and he admits
You know, he's falling rated exaggerating the PDF term, which is like, you know really should be reserved for children, you know
Um, you know, he's also taking, um, severity away from the word and the question is why
lightly.
Okay.
You know how I have my thoughts about the word and I G G E R. Right.
Right.
Now that's a word that I think that the strength of it needs to be diminished.
But I think that the word P E D O P H I L E. I think the strength of that word needs
Right, and it's just it is not going to be if it's applied to every single person and any situation of anything under the age of a
like so 17 days or 17 years
364 days is like they're trying to make this distinction of that's gonna be a PDF as opposed to a normal a normal
site like person and it's like
it's it's crazy that
You know, I do think that the other words like a feeba file and things like that should be like more recognized as
what you know, maybe as perhaps less severe than the PDF.
And so, you know, that would bring strength back
to the word if, you know, there's more distinctions made
as opposed to like even calling, he's like,
he's like, well, a 20 year old is a child in my eyes.
Like that he was saying, like he's like, so.
Really?
Yeah, he was saying, so a 20-year-old, he would call it a child because he's 32 or 34 or whatever.
He's like, I look at a 20-year-old and I see that as a young child, like a young child.
And so, just like they were saying about Benny, like Benny's 24, Joker's 26.
You know, I hit more on Joker, you know, openly than I have.
I did on Benny and it's mostly, it's mostly, you know, for anything.
Okay. Well, I mean, if that's the case, then I, then...
Why is he not speaking out more so in regards to quite a few women who have been photographed by the Playboy Enterprise?
you know, as soon as someone's 18, they can be photographed by a playboy or be in the adult legal entertainment industry.
Um, I mean, I have thought for years that the age should be raised to 25, but that's not going to happen.
Um, and who are you going to bring up, Tracy Lords?
Well, Tracy Lords, she went to Redondo.
I know that situation.
Yeah, and she was 17, but we used a fake ID to get into the industry.
And then so everything, I did recall all their videos as child porn.
They sure did.
And that wasn't any of the producer's fault.
I mean, really, that was her.
Or it also, I think her mother was involved in that also, which was.
Sad when I think I know Jenna Jamison. I think got a job at a strip club at like 16
He did and he had a brother pull off her braces with pliers and stuff like that
Yeah, so she can pass for like 18 and so there's pretty crazy stories of the
industry and you know a lot of
The most popular genres, I think right now are like trans and teen. I think those are like, you know
Teen has always been one of the most popular and you know, there's actually I
don't know if the if they still do this, but there used to be a
Graphical map that showed which genres of adult entertainment were most popular in whatever region of the country
It's in the Bible belt. Yeah that the most risque
Things are the most popular
A lot of Texas Republicans like whenever the whenever they had like these conventions all of a sudden the gay grinder like we started crashing because
So many people like
You would never yeah when they're all this convention
Yeah, I'm something in Texas, but
Yeah, and so it's always like, you know, just like Kinsey, I guess in his studies like, you know
He he showed gay pornography and regular pornography to people that put electrodes on their testicles and stuff
And the people that identified as most homophobic had the most sexual reaction
To the gay. That's why they're very homophobic. Yeah
They're afraid they can turn any second. They're afraid. They're attracted to some of these fem boys or twinks
Yeah, well nobody turns it just is what you are at whatever phase of life you're in
You know, some people are always hetero some people are always lgbtq some people
Shift that that's the sexual fluidity
Yeah, and I think most people you know do shift throughout their life and to some
degree, whether they admit it or not.
Well, yeah, and I think like there's like I know my my parents were friends with a couple couples that were I was very suspect as
Like it's like, you know
The husband seemed very gay and the you know and people it was kind of those all it's common
Look, it's very well. I mean as you know, I'm I'm the physical as is my sibling
my dad was openly lgbtq and
Initially at the first
Portion of his life, you know, he lived as hetero and then the second portion of his life life
He lived as lgbtq. So he would have been be by in my opinion. Yeah, but
that's more common than I think people realize but if you're very
Rigid I guess in your ways and you know, you're somebody who is I guess from a very
was considered conservative today,
that would be a very scary thing for some people.
Right, and then there was this guy, Ted Haggard,
I don't know if he was a minister,
he was one of those super church guys,
and then he got caught doing meth
and getting with the gay porn star massage therapist,
I guess, like doing stuff with him.
Really?
And he was totally blackballed from his church.
They basically sent him and his family,
because he's married with several kids,
and they sent him and his family to the...
basically like the, I guess, Arizona or something like that. And, you know, he totally lost all his, you know,
basically his exile. Well, I mean, in that case, I mean, what I feel is wrong in that case is it's not
the sexuality, it's him being dishonest. Right. And, you know, it,
see, when that kind of thing happens, whoever the wife is, the mom of the kids, it's very hurtful.
And it does
effect there, you know, I know firsthand, not from my but just, you know,
yeah, you can see on her face, she had that smile, that like that plaster on
smile, like, you know, and like the whole time and like was like, but basically
you could tell she was going through.
She was just putting on a face because she was going through like this hell and like the whole family and the kids were
Teenagers and stuff and they're hearing these stories about their dad and blah blah blah. It's actually a great
It was an HBO documentary on it
I'm gonna try to look for it because it was on YouTube for a while and it's just really interesting
Ted haggard that was a big scandal back in 2012 and also like they ever remember like the
Trinity broadcasting that work at that lady with the hair Jan Crouch and her husband had a gay
a huge gay scandal too. I'm not surprised considering how I mean she was very
kind of like almost like a caricature you know and a male and I'm not saying this is always the case
but oftentimes men who are attracted to hyper caricature rise like feminine kind of
Looks yeah, and to also be into
Transsexuals or trannies, whatever you wanted to find that as yeah, um, it's
Even the boy thing is that way a lot of a lot of straight guys are like
Talking about the fem fem boys now or whatever just like I don't know if you heard like they're basically
Guys that kind of look like girls like, you know, like they're so family very feminine guys
I don't know which would they do then which they didn't used to be in vogue really
I was like they're kind of like
It's kind of normalized with the younger generation nowadays, which is surprising to me. I'm surprised by that but
You know to each their own. I mean things were simpler. I guess
Well, yeah generation coming up, but it was also more
hurtful if you didn't fit a certain mold yeah
Yeah, and there's always been a gay undercurrent to in this in society especially since like the film industry started
But it's like you know up until like the 70s when it was considered a mental disorder
Like everything was very negative in the portrayals and like as serial killers
as, you know, this dangerous people, if you look at, there's also like this thing about trans people
being very dangerous and, you know, very, like doing school shootings and things like that. We
had a few trans school shooters recently and, you know, it's kind of makes it, it's basically, you know,
scare people away from the community or I'm most afraid of the hetero neglectful
mothers that's who I'm most afraid of they did yeah I did see a video today of
somebody that you know talking about how they were smoking cigarettes when
they're pregnant and what and they think it's fine to smell not a good idea yeah
But yeah, I'm really um, I'm glad a few things have happened. Um, I'm
Your prop your panel is like the only panel that I'm willing to join within these communities. Um
You know, no no aggressive hate toward other people, but I think I've pretty much made it clear
I don't want anything to do with certain people at this point and
Oh, you know what? I heard someone talking about me recently saying that I was full of
SHIT because
I can't, they were saying that I'm, I can't get IVF.
First off, how I'm going to attempt my motherhood
is nobody's business, whether it's natural conception or IVF.
But the cutoff age for that is actually nowadays 51.
They were saying that it was impossible for me to do IVF
because the cutoff was allegedly 45.
No, it's 51.
Some places 55.
So, yeah, I mean, it's a guess. Yeah, it's definitely
That is possible. I mean the medic medical
Like a revolution. I think you're your videos frozen. I'm sorry. Yeah, there's medical Revolut
There's revolutions happening medically, right? It's like they are able to
To do a lot of things. I mean, I think they're gonna be increasing the lifespan of people maybe like by a hundred years
I think but with the breakthroughs that our people are having and
Well, there's a lot of women. I mean, especially
black or african-american women who are um and i didn't i did a stream about it
there's a lot of black african-american women who are celebrities who had their children later
and you know i was thinking about it and it's just a lot of it has to do with
you're so busy and you have so much up against you
If you want to achieve a certain level of success or financial security when you're younger being a woman of color that you really kind of don't have the chance to attempt to be a parent until you're older, if you're trying to be responsible about it, or maybe you didn't even realize you wanted to be a parent until you're older.
I didn't have to share publicly when it comes to that, but then to be so negative about it,
you know, um, I really hope that certain women who, you know, they can take issue with me for
whatever reason, but especially if they're mothers of daughters basically, um, wishing ill will upon
me, I hope that their daughters are not treated in the same regard if their daughters walk a path
similar to mine in life, which could happen.
That's really all I have to say about that. But yeah, the cutoff for IVF nowadays is 51 to 55
Have you seen my my newest video? I've made a music video. You're just a it's up. Yeah, let's watch
This is called boycott blues. Okay. Oh, okay. So here's this is the latest
video I
Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day Day
and the grudge in the chest on the hella boycott
like he's leading the quads, everybody exposed
and nobody got proof, just recycled guys
have been a nicotine booth, talkin' home with money
platform chaos, fake out rage, drippin' like
dollar store makeup, one minute predators, next minute
they laugh, hold when they're built like a
psychological draft, Christine Sterity
then pretendin' she's neutral, backdoor whispers
into that feudal, everybody worried about
real life threats, but they live stream drama
to fool me though.
Now the A.I. daughters abandoned in space, meanwhile bit a little trove foam at the phase, everybody preaching while begging for views, internet vultures singing, boycott blues, fade out with static, cat hiss, cheap vape crackle, you can actually watch me.
different for you I don't I don't think you've done a uh it was more of a different
yeah so I mean a rap kind of sound in a while I like it there's a pop and a rap in there and
then makes it with blues
and you pick a music type.
It has a little Southern twang to it at the end.
Right, yeah.
Because you can, there's actually, there's, okay,
so the person in the chat is asking,
do I pick a music type?
Yes, and you can do fusion of it
because they gave you like a hundred music types.
And so you can choose a bunch of them,
you can optimize the prompt for the type of music,
you know, automatically on there.
It's really cool.
The program, my use or whatever,
I've been really happy with the results.
It's not Suno. It's a different one, but I'll tell you if anyone wants to know, but
Um, no, don't tell your secrets
No, no, no, like maybe maybe whenever you decide to retire tell but no don't don't don't don't do that
Okay
Leg up on your competition. Come on now. Thank you. Yeah, I know. Yeah. I'm a secret formula. I can't share so
So yeah, but
Yeah, I'll just say there's great the technology is actually
Like an assistant. I mean, it's like if you have talent it will amplify the talent
And so I do think I have some kind of talent in the visuals and like the ideas for the songs and the and then lyricism
And so I and then then the rest the talents that I don't have like, you know playing musical instruments and you know
Sound engineering, you know, that can kind of get taking like all the
professionals are using the AI at least as song starters
nowadays. And I think before we even publicly had the
technology
um you know houses like disney probably uh industrial light and magic were using some
of the tools and the music industry definitely music industry for years has been even if even
i mean even with like auto tune and things like that like people are thinking oh your ai music
but then it's like look at bringing spears that's basically ai music it's like they take her vocals
they think they create whatever they want her to say and they put it in it sounds good especially
you know yeah it's it's been AI for a long time. Yeah yeah yeah I mean it's like the
animation of yeah absolutely and it's like even like the maybe script generation or some of the
jokes or things like that I mean it's like companies you know this does save companies a
lot of money on hiring writers and you know and other expensive things but there but the thing
music and stuff. There's no copyrights on it. And so you can play, I can play really cool.
There's people that are way more talented than I. I mean, they put Hollywood behind it, then all
of a sudden you've got really amazing stuff. But I think I'm not doing bad for just being a single
person doing the whole, you know, working with. Right. And it's like, because there's teams of
people, like, you know, they can really afford like a lot of stuff to make amazing things. I'm just
you know generating the videos, putting them together, editing it with the song that I wrote and
you know and so I think that's a lot of my talent put into it but it's also I couldn't do it without
the technology right now but just like an accountant couldn't do it on an abacus you know it's much
And it's not considered strictly AI once you do inject your own editing into it. Okay. And you're
starting to do that more so. So give yourself a little bit more credit. You're not just AI music.
Eventually what I foresee you doing is actually getting a little bit into music production.
add some of your own composition into it.
I do write a lot of it, or at least I'll write something,
and then it will put it into basically the right cadence,
and the right, so it's good for the song, you know?
But it's like there is so much of me in it.
They're not just generated,
and I go over hundreds of images,
for the right ones to animate for the thing
and put it together in a certain way.
And even like, and they'll be these great synchronicities
that I won't even try to make,
but it will like, they'll just like,
it just comes together so perfectly sometimes.
Yeah.
Like how, yeah, it goes in the video.
So yeah, I love working with it.
It's basically what I've been waiting for.
It's because I do have talents, but it's like,
It's just it's like, you know, you can have talents
But it's like when you have it something that can like actually put them out there and put them into like, you know
A visual audio visual form. Okay, then it's like, yeah
So Nancy, thank you so much.
And the app using it owns the copyrights, yeah.
But hey, thing that is, I haven't seen the thing
that is in a while.
One day I'm going to do a stream about the intricacies
of the legalities in regards to exactly what the AI apps own
versus what they don't, what's considered transformative.
I mean, even just changing the musical key
voids the copyright.
There's a lot of.
Things that people don't quite understand, you know, it's not really a lump umbrella
Thing and when it comes down to it company. I use Berliner
Yes, like when you subscribe you do you do get the copyright to the songs and so yes
When you subscribe, whoever that is doesn't know what they're talking about. They're just being contrary for the hell of it
Yeah, that's just a troll troll move. I need to reduce my troll. Hey, I see Alexander
I mean, I think I didn't update the codex to fix a lot of things. Oh
Okay, I'll take a look at it
And I started the psychonomicon.
I started, I started, and so it's like, it's
Wait, what is it?
Psychonomicon.
What is that?
That's like every, it's like basically putting a storyline to the show.
Okay.
So, and so, and it's basically putting a mythology also into it.
Cause I have it.
It's about 75.
I haven't.
Haven't looked at it. So I got to do another
Stream, you know, I'm not even gonna look at it yet. I'm gonna do a stream that way you get my initial reaction
I can look at it. I like I'm looking at it right now and already see that you changed the front page a little bit
Yeah, so I'll do that. Um either late tonight or tomorrow. It'd be awesome. I will
And I love, and last time I was able to take like your episode and I took that and I said,
can you put this into actionable steps to improve my website? And it's able to do that.
You know, put them in there to the, you know, my coding, my coding thing, where do my coding?
And then all of a sudden it's like, it's, I'm able to put your suggestions in there like,
like that. And it's like so cool. Wow. Yeah. And so that's what I did. I did put a lot of your
Fixed like though, you know, I think I try to put all your your episodes in now
I made sure to hyperlink your show your pages
I have to fix some I have to fix the IP 21 because I thought it was a website
But um, but then I so I kind of think I want to do a boycott song
When I think about it, maybe I could merge that with my review
My update of my review on your codex. Okay. I have an idea. I'll do I'll do a little something
Happy great. Yeah, yeah, awesome. And yeah, your show's been great. I always enjoy watching you
I love your sense of humor and did you watch blogger?
He was in a motel room the other night
and like he went out and he found $20 bill.
That's pretty crazy.
Like I don't really find $20 bills everywhere,
but he said he's found like, you know,
a dollar, a $10 bill, then a $20 bill.
So, you know, I do believe that-
Sounds almost like somebody is baiting him.
Did, you know, there's a, there's a,
no, there's actually a warning.
I remember,
Relative of mine sent me a thing on Facebook warning people if you see a 20 on the ground do not pick it up because
people are like putting some sort of like chemical on it
that it immediately gets into your skin
to where they can abduct you
that they're specifically going after women.
But blogger is like, look,
he might as well be a little woman.
He's so little.
Oh my God.
He's getting, you know, it's interesting.
I feel like it's blogger trying to be you
at this point completely.
I think he is.
I think he's gonna disappear soon, but if he's finding all these 20s
It sounds I think someone's putting that money out for him
And it's trying to like lure him somewhere because he looks like a little
He's so little I didn't realize how little he is until he was in McDonald's
I saw a part of one of his recent streams and he set up his camera. He went to the counter and
Just the expression on the guy behind the counter's face when blogger was walking up. It was priceless
I mean he's a little
He's he's like a little imp
Yeah, like a leprechaun or something like that. Yeah, it's a little blogger con, but
Yeah, he was in a hotel room the other night. It looks like he's been like, you know
Doing something working. He says he's like, I made all this money this week
And he's like, but he just wanted to like sleep in the hotel room and
I kind of had a I had a weird dream about it that he porn bomb himself and he was like naked on his stream and stuff like that
It was a strange dream. I was sure you were dreaming was it?
It could have been I had asked the next day
I was like was that a dream and everyone's like that wasn't dream
He wasn't for bombing himself because I dreamed he had like no pants on and I don't know
And it was very it was very explicit. I was like, oh my god. He's gonna get in trouble for porn bombing
But yeah, I guess it was just a dream.
Yeah, he has so much to say, but he always takes his lives down.
I mean, I know that they're syndicated over on the rumble thing.
Yeah.
But he's.
I have a hard time watching him now because I feel like he's going to be one of those to where any day now
We just get some bad news and you know, I don't like to watch that kind of thing at this point
But he was annoying. I guess he was annoying all the neighbors in the hotel
They were all saying shut up because he was loud being loud live streaming all night and stuff
But it was yeah, well, I guess he's gonna be arrested or something because
I mean the thing about the city that he lives in you think about Spokane as being like a major city
It's it's really almost a small town not many people live there
Most people never leave there. It's kind of removed from the rest of the country and by the way
I'm good times. This is in prison or jail right now
No way. Is that rumor or real really?
I heard he's really in jail right now.
He's checked in for his DUI or something like that.
So I don't know.
I thought it was a year in jail.
So that might be, I guess a year in jail
is probably like a week or something like that.
The one in the LA that would be,
I'm not sure in his area,
but I think he like took a year.
So he did like, did he drive drunk again?
Is that what it was?
I think it was the same one.
Is if anyone knows the truth,
what happened, because I saw he was on the other night
and then the next day.
I'm gonna look it up right now.
I know how to look it up.
He's a Michigan
Yeah, I
They're like, you know
whoa
Well, I don't know if this is the
Current let's see
He just talked about it quicker than I signed him, but yeah, let's say somebody else. Let's see
In California, you can get the mug shots because mine would probably be out there
They're not but he's in jail like he's actually in jail right now
I heard I mean you guys if anyone knows information about it
I like yesterday and chat they were saying you know a good times. He's in jail now
He checked himself in you know good luck in jail and stuff and so
Yeah, I don't know and I did see like he did he like streaming the other night
But then he didn't stream since then, you know, so I
Don't that was his
He discussed it. He was just on beat. Oh, he was just on beat. Well, maybe he's already out. I don't know
Okay, so he's on beat is 10 minutes. Maybe it's yeah, I
But you know what 42 people in my chat, okay, he needs to stop drinking period
I mean just don't drink anymore. Okay. Well, I see I see the April 5th thing. Yeah
Okay, maybe maybe I got bad information. I don't I don't know. Maybe he's been I know
I got I got six months in jail and I spent three days in jail
And so that's how it kind of sometimes works like that, you know
He was like officially I could have done like two weeks community servers
I don't drink ten days community service and I got three, you know, three days time served or whatever
He was streaming then he was in beta stream. Well, why does it come over here now? Is he part of the boycott?
I want to know I want to know if he's part of the boycott, but um, he's the definition of boycott
Yeah, okay, so I see the initial mug shy and it's on this thing called busted busted newspaper. I see that it
I mean, how does he look in the mug if you have I can share the
I remember when people were first circulating it, I thought
it was AI. I didn't think it was good or something.
He looks like himself. It looks like he's at home in
front of his green screen actually but it's a gray background
instead of green. They never let me smile at my mug shots.
What's up easy good to see 42 people in the chat. Yes, exactly.
And it's like so anyone says I'm over whatever it's like
There are people that still support me and it's like and people I think they're actually the smarter people and so I'm happy to
Have like the dumb people gone and like just having the smart people who are actually the question
You know, but Alexander they were going over in CA's chat. They were talking about their their their their a strategy
And that is well, we're gonna we're gonna be a strategy
Yeah, they're gonna be the anti PDF group and then so any other group that is against them is considered PDFs, right?
and so
that and so they and then they're but they don't build a crush on those. Well that's going to be a
very tough thing for them to adhere to considering certain alliances that they have. I mean they're
always one degree of separation away from people who have been labeled be it justifiably or not
Right and beat is not even live, so I don't know if it was him or they're talking about that was on earlier
Or maybe they're just being told maybe they saw a rerun
I don't know if anyone has good information about it. I'll put the link up and you know you can come tell us about it
Long but you know RG porn bomb me
Q porn bomb me you were there on Q porn bomb me Arthur is now saying oh cues the hero of the community because cues spearheaded this boycott against me
They got Kate saying boycott me and promoting Tony who's the hero now.
He's supposed to be a hero.
Yeah.
Well, Sam is the hero cause Sam and kicked off psyche off his show.
Everyone wants to be the hero.
They want to be the new Avengers or something and RG form bomb me too.
But RG is backstage when he did it.
Yeah.
So I, he didn't get up doing it, but he tried to put, yeah, he puts a big,
penis in the mouth backstage several times, but I was like, okay, well, no one can see that except for me. And like, yeah, things. But, um, yeah. And so
Well two days ago good times posted a post yeah on his community tab
So I mean unless he was put in jail over the past two days and yeah
That's what I think. I think it's a false rumor. It was yesterday. I think I think it was yesterday morning. Oh yesterday
Yeah, so like two days ago was like his last string. I haven't seen him since then he hasn't been live today
So that person was just lying so
Hmm
Well, um, I don't I mean I've I've had so many back and forth for good times
To me, he's such old news at this point
Yeah, I think that he's just ridiculous and I wish him the best but
When it comes to those, you know DUIs, that's not really a joke. He and just for his own health
He needs to talk tone it down, but yeah, you know, maybe he doesn't want to different people do different things Wow
Wow, but yeah, so they're gonna be the Avengers
Avenging nothing I guess not going after anything that really
Matters I have me and it's like it says like the new retarded
Cuties or just disabled cuties or something like that. Oh god. I don't know the picture was pictures were on it
I can't I can't recognize anybody else really, but I
Love it. It's supposed to be
I don't know I guess but it's like the Aaron I guess was Crystal Marie's pick or Crystal Anne's picture
And I guess like they're trying to you know, she I guess she was probably one of the disabled cuties
I think I mean, it's like right. I mean, I don't know what happened with her and Aaron Carter, but
You know, if he hadn't met some of these people he had law enforcement involved with her at the end
I mean, we know there are suicide baiters like that. I mean, we do know that. I mean, it's like, you know
Honestly, she's she's just sometimes people just have a bad spirit and she's one of them. That's my opinion
Bad person
Yeah, but I
Think oh, sorry
the improvements in it and the stories.
Also, I want to show you, I'll leave you a sneak preview.
They do have something called,
if you go to Psychinomicon, okay?
It will show, if you scroll to the bottom,
it will just say something like relationship.
Or really, yeah, you can look at the entity network,
click on that and look at this.
So I'm gonna share this page.
This is, I think with your premium,
but look at this, see this is a circle right there?
Okay, and so it's all it's every really all the relationships everybody on the page
Maps and how they connect really? Oh, I love this. Let me look up. Well, I'm gonna have to look at this
I'm on my end right now. I have to yeah, I did not know that you did that
Okay now now now we're rocking
Yeah, because it's gonna go through all the relationship match mapping. It's a knowledge graph. Yeah
Now we're rocking
Okay, now now where is this on here? I just posted in my chat if you're in the chat
You can see like the cold codex the page psychonomicon
Yeah, wait am I logged in yeah, yeah, yeah, let me let me just uh
E and T
Let me let me okay. I'm looking at it right now. Let's see. Let's look at this. Oh
Very nice
I started importing it and so the more
Episodes I do the more connections are gonna be made and the more but yeah, you can click up. Yeah
now this this
I'll have to make it clickable, I guess, like clickable and hyperlinked, but it's just showing.
No, I love this. I love this. Okay, now. This is what I'm talking about.
So, yeah, and this is, there's gonna be cool things like this. I'm gonna have things in
Here's the ones that are listed as summaries of terror and so they're basically a lot of shorts in the music videos so far
I can actually go to my admin and
Keep generating the episode I've been generating the episodes today and
and it's creating these entries in the psychonomic concept.
Everything is also summarized,
all the relationships are mapped,
all the topics are mapped.
There's, I added thousands of more things.
And so, and everything, also all the episodes
are unprivated right now.
And so you can see.
Awesome.
Okay, I'm not gonna look too much yet
because I want to do a stream initial,
but I'm glad you told me about this.
Yeah, very nice, it'll be very nice to see the relationships
You didn't know people had or people that knew each other
Things like that
Nice
Nice everyone my website is cold codex.me I
Do recommend it like cuz I don't have memberships on the show right now
Or they might be I think they're still are working for me or I see that I see that I get the icon the emojis and stuff
but I
Think they are suspended for the time being until I my strike and but my strikes aspire whatever but
You can't you can't wait. Yeah, there's really cool stuff on that website and also I'm gonna have like my live streams connected to it
I might be able to connect it right now. I
Put it put it and it should stay on my website
Like the video of the current stream with the chat on it if I go
Yeah, I noticed the last time I was looking at it that it had the
Latest but not but like a live now thing. So yeah
Yeah, so I'm really excited. So I have the admin panel working now, you know live stream. Let me see if I can just do it
It's a go live
Okay, and let's see if it did it. Okay, so it says live
And so I do, I think maybe now if you go to Kolkotek,
you can go to the live stream part of it and it should.
I'm sure the video of this live stream right now that we're on over there
Since I turned it on so I mean I do have there's such cool things
I'm able to do with this website and this is just the beginning. I want people to be able especially everybody join every
I'm telling y'all
See, this is why you don't need to worry about your naysayers
They're all gonna be crawling back to you because you are creating something very unique that they're all gonna want to be a part of
And they're just jealous right now, and they don't want you to create what you're creating, but keep going
Keep going because this is more than a stream
You're sure
Well, i'm i'm i'm getting ready i i'm not saying exactly what i'm up to i'm up to some things but um
But you do we bring me some things I'm up to will be interesting. This is gonna be an interesting year
I think for both of us in a lot of ways
Yes, and so everybody make sure you subscribe to Alexandra and she does
Great streams. Oh, so so now on them. So now if you go to Colt codex
It will say currently live in a banner and it says my live stream if I click the arrow
I think it should take you to
There's no stream schedule. Okay, so I need to do some work on it
But there's also a notify me place there people put their email address and so at least tell you when my stream goes live
It'll just email you a notification. I
Can enable also push notifications. Okay, it says block. So I need to do some work on the site still
These are untested features and things and sometimes it takes a little bit, but I think you guys will be more than happy with the contents as they are
I think it's totally worth them
Like you're a fan of the show you you almost have to be a part of cult codex
Dot me because it's a companion to what you're doing now and it really draws you more into your streams, right?
Instead of doing Patreon or anything like that, I'm just doing this and so this is like the way to also support the channel
even if you're not like really into
the advanced like because you can also half a million transcripts at least or half a million transcript segments that you can search
and then analyze and
You can do all kinds behind me all kinds of really really cool features
And so I think you guys would want to be part of this, but if you're not interested it is a way to support me
Beyond the members like you know having the members of YouTube. I didn't even have commercials
So there's no reason to say or advertisers won't like this
And and of course I had was the membership and it's like and they're gonna be jerks and like turn it off because they're like
Okay, well, you know you have some content that might be AI on your channel and so
You know and they're doing to a lot of people people that are way more subscribers than me way more
They had relied on YouTube way more than I do but still
I'll get the monetization back and I'll get monetized on the other channel, too
I mean it's like without easily I'm already qualified on both channels. You know the other channel almost qualified
I need a few more subscribers, but you know
I will get the monetization back in,
but I don't think anybody else has this kind of website.
And also when you're even the above premium,
you can put your own.
And if you're a streamer, you're gonna want this.
It's like, you'll have your episodes added to the code text.
And there can be the little-
And also if you're a streamer looking to, you know,
put yourself out there a little bit more,
you are gonna wanna join the call seriously
because psyche streams,
consistently and if you just want to be a part of something like I think it's like like I'm not
someone who's so much of someone who likes to be a part of much of anything but this is different
so you know if you're a streamer who's you know kind of looking to put yourself out there you might
With this now because you might not have the opportunity to later
Yeah, because this is the beginning and so I have like this kind of prices and things like that
But I mean I'm gonna put so much content and material and useful thing and advertising for people
I'll put so much in there that it's just like we stupid not to get it like because it's like
You'll be people will be promoted. I can show when other live streamers are on I guess the notifications for other live streamers I can
catalog all your episodes and put a lore to that too.
And when you're the upper subscriber, yeah.
So my mic doesn't work when I'm not eating, I know.
I need to put a sandwich in my mouth
and it'll be able to hear me again, right?
But you'll love it, you'll love it.
And I did try to put all the music videos on,
I have to just make sure and like confirm it
and stuff like that because
You know we love your music videos like you know I just shared the bbsb
Well, I'm not going to reveal exactly what I'm going to be up to the rest of the year
Okay, but I'm going to be delving heavy heavy heavy heavy heavy into putting out a lot of music
Okay, it's going to be a lot so you know I think he'll enjoy it
I think so
It's going to be a little bit more than just music too, but I don't want anyone to know what I'm up to
Yeah, so someone says YouTube is just updated as TOS and is and is I'm on has about 40% of channels
Really?
Yeah, they have to do the TOS without telling anybody change the rules
Without getting people a chance to like to like fix their channel based on the rules
Also, they don't tell you exactly why they're why they're taking up your channel
They don't say what what episode it was the triggered it or whatever and they're not
Also watching the video they ask you to do a video reply to it. They're not even watching that. There's a video reply
Yeah, a video you want to see if people are real or what?
Okay, I see what they're doing. Yeah, they want a video appeal
But they don't even look at it like I had zero it had zero views and they say make it unlisted and then we'll just be the
even like
So, I mean also I'll move all my AI all the major AI because I am mostly a live streaming channel
But I do put my AI videos on here. I'll move on on to another channel
That's no problem and I can apply for it a couple months, but it's like I can't well
There's one strike on the channel. I can't reapply it so
But I will and you know and so
But yeah, and no matter what happens to the channel,
I'll have the codex.
I have the last year has been on a stream or a rumble.
And so I'll have, all the videos are still gonna be up.
If I have to link all the rumble videos
to what's currently there, I can.
And then I'll have my backup channel.
My backup channel is gonna monetize.
So I'm not in bad shape.
I'm not.
And I'm gonna be okay.
I mean they can freeze your money and stuff
That'll all come back when I'm remodeled
I'm not even concerned. I know exactly what to do. I
Know exactly their ankle. They're going I got
That's why I say when it comes to the haters, okay
You have to
Really ignore at this point and just do what you are supposed to be doing when it comes to developing
What you're creating for yourself because the haters they're not gonna survive this cleansing process that I guess Google or YouTube is doing
Okay, you need to just push forward with creating your future
This is your future that you are making.
Yes.
We got Katie we got we got a Jamie in the chat
I also have I hope you had a great time the other night with Joni like I think Joni was oh, I did
Well, I was talking about it on my most recent stream on my alexandra channel
Because I I still haven't done an official. I was telling her I wanted to make an official
introduction for my page by page Bible reading, but
She but I was
If I hadn't had that conversation with her and you that night, I wouldn't have had the interest to look into the Christian Kabbalah.
And I'm very excited about learning about that right now, but I was talking about her and that conversation and, you know, looking into elements of the Christian Kabbalah on my last or my latest Bible reading.
So I'm just going to be so much about spirituality over the next few years
I just feel my own spirit opening in that direction right now
Yeah, and I want to take some of my streaming in that direction also
I want to be about music and spirituality. That's where I'm like
happiest
Go for it, go for it.
And someone's asking if I've met ghosts recently.
Ghost texted me last night.
Ghost has also been on the show recently.
It's really unfair how he's being treated.
They keep playing this 20 year old woman on panels, Alex.
And she's 20 years old, but she's slow.
And then Ghost texted her backstage,
hey, here's my phone number.
She called the police on him and stuff
for calling her or whatever.
But.
Really we know ghost is a really harmless person like he's an asshole. He's a jerk. He's like he's he's kind of dumb
Maybe he's a little bit slow too. We don't know but he's still he's a good heart
And that's what I really look for and uh, and then Alex McQueen wants to call him a a PDF now
Yeah, I read him again. It's McQueen doing this. I don't know. I don't know. Yeah
He's influenced by RG
Yeah, I mean, it's like, I mean, yeah, it's like
And ghost is a really harmless, but it's like why are they letting this woman on panel in the first place if it's like
You can't talk to her and it's like people are saying well
She's a cat fish to get people in trouble and you know
And then Alex is talking to this other disabled woman named grace who's crying on a dime and
Alex can I talk to you backstage please? Oh, they're speaking on me and he's okay. I think
Ghost just needs to return to his regularly scheduled programming. You know, if he wants to
be on your panel, he should join whatever he wants to. I thought he was going to even start his own,
he was saying he wanted to start his own podcast.
How do you how does he know that this is just an effort to try to stifle him from moving forward in a pot?
I think it is I think that if you hear migos you need to do what you want to do and just ignore these weirdos
um
Yeah, and he's upset no
He really was upset because he had people turn on him for this situation when they're like actually having this person on their show
and basically trying to
Has something to talk about by anybody talking to her and it's just it's really ridiculous and and why he thought these people were his friends
He text message me practically crying about the stuff like cuz he's like what he doesn't understand what he did and
Then he needs to be labeled. Well, he didn't do anything illegal. He didn't do anything wrong either
I mean, I would suggest to him in the future. Maybe
Develop more of a rapport with somebody before you call them if if that's what some of this is about, but
I think that he should block these people and...
Go on with whatever it is that he wants to do and goes to some of a show he goes under Tyler
I don't know if I would have posted his chat. I wanted to get it
I think he'll do a good show like I think he he loves he likes to talk. Yeah
The Bain and talk and he's like and now he's like and I think I might have inspired him
like I've inspired a few people to to start their own shows and
And so I'm really excited that they do because we need more places to go hang out. It's like it is like
And besides people that are just like have their whole shows about me bad mouthing me or or bad mouthing Alex. I mean, it's like
You know, but I seem like a topic on every show I've ever like I don't know if it's me
But every time I go into a chat, it's like me and you were being discussed and
It's like wow like we are like the some stars that would be to say to be discussed so much for everyone to say
We're so we are the stars right now. You know, and they're so they're so invested also, you know
I think I had it. I think was either just Jen or it was
Or I don't know if the porn star person or I don't know if there's some rogue mod
It's when I had a modded and they hit everyone in my chat literally everyone. Yeah, it was probably her
She's very envious of me. Yeah, and so and I did get into like a conflict with her
I had this like really good philosophical religious discussion with thing that is the other night
And it's like I don't know if he enjoyed it as much as I did. No problem Jamie
Yeah, and Jamie's a really good Jamie. I've been yeah, I made Jamie a mod
She was in my thing the other night when I was looking into the cabala and whatnot. She's yeah
She is very sweet and Jamie's awesome and it's like but she's been with me before even the show and she's been in almost every episode
She's very very loyal person
It's just you know, it's like she has a she lives on it in California. She has a bee farm
I guess I guess they go sell bee
Items to the market. I don't know if I'm right about that Jamie
But I know you raise bees and and things like that and and sales of the farmers market and stuff
And she wasn't a bad accident, you know about it about a year. Just look at all the hate though like you're advertising
Okay, you you are a star right now, okay?
You want to maintain your star status. You don't want to go
You know like an actual star in the sky can go supernova or it can go it can diminish
You don't want to diminish you you want to but you don't want to go supernova either
You just kind of want to twinkle for a while you want to twinkle. Yeah
Yeah, I think that is did like the phyllis off. He said he did like the phyllis pulse. Yeah, we had we were talking
You know about we thought we got an o'clock or orange. We got into
Adams, it was like, you know, I got I don't know
Do his own show, I think I think he should you know, I know that he
You know wants to keep things on a certain level
But he's he would be a good panel host. I think he would be too. I think he would be too
And he's in maybe one day. I mean that's yeah, well, you don't got so many days left. Mr
You are getting up there. I mean, I know you're you're kind of rocking the young guy looks still but
Just saying, you know, there's no day like today
Alex I want to show you what I guess like the sweet pea person is posted and Sam see Sam going bald again
But I just want to show you the picture. She posted on me. It's like you aren't okay. I see this is my fault
I'm sorry that when we were going back and forth. I
I can't see it. You're frozen
They're gonna take it off because I'm trying to bring up I mean I'm trying to bring up this the latest picture because
And I what I don't think was your fault. I mean it's like I think like
I don't know who started, I thought that she like
posts me bald first and it kind of spread.
Cause it's like, I do have these,
I say this is where my horns used to be
when I look at my hairline.
Cause I do have, my dad had these too.
We also have this little thing on our ears.
They have like a little dimple on our ears
when it goes down on the side of it.
Like, and we always saw these are like, hey,
well, the AI based on you, but the horns looks great.
I mean, people love that.
That that is a look for you. I almost kind of wish I could put horns on you for real because it works for you
Right, even you know saying saying always good psyche. He was the psyche he goes like that
He does like that a sign when he does okay, so serious
But here's that it says psyche and he's use some sunscreen so you can Alexander you can see this is exaggerated or not
I'm gonna pull this this chat into this browser. Can I do that? Yeah
Hold on a second. I'm gonna pull the chat into the browser pose from a sweet pea
Okay, let me get that out there goes okay, okay, so here I'm gonna okay now need to bring the string yard into it shit
Where's this Jamie? I'm gonna be
So delving into the angels and demons this year. You are gonna be very happy
Don't worry. Don't I will not deprive you of things having to do with angels and demons at all
I'm not saying exactly what I'm up to but you're gonna have fun. Don't worry
Yeah, good. Yeah, okay, so I'll just get the sweepy link here's this so this is the this is the post that she's posting
I just have to move to this browser because okay, so this is where my stream yard is okay, so oh it's that girl
She's weird
Yeah, she's my first member of my show and she's like always in the chat, but she's obsessed with me
Like she did the whole whole channel was just me and like a lot of it was just funny
But yeah, so here's what she posted to me today. I went to the store. I got a new camera
I got a new phone. So I got a new camera and the new camera is very
Let's just say it's a very like, you know detailed or whatever very up close and uh
Let me see if I get do you hear me still or they close my thing? Okay here. Well, I don't see what you're presenting
That's what I'm waiting for. I'm looking for my
Stream yard. Okay. I need to close this. Okay. There we go. Close that close that. Okay
Well, okay, I found I found those I found us. Okay, so here it is. This is sweet peas page of
My latest when I went outside. Okay, so this is it right here share
Yeah
So I mean, it's horrifying like okay, so she got that okay, so there's my hairline
It looks like it looks like gray hair first of all now
Wait a minute. This is the girl who never shows herself on camera and she's doing this
Look at it. I have like all this like I mean it looks like I'm 70
I think did she not put an AI at 35? Well, scroll it down. Well, okay. What is what is the channel?
Okay, I'm just gonna go the channel is sweet P. Yeah, sweet P sweet P
The space PHC, a sweet peeing.
and she took down most of her videos,
but it's like, I don't look like that.
I don't have gray hair first of all.
I have zero gray hairs.
Second of all, I'm not bald like that.
Third of all, I don't have this like Freddy Krueger,
whatever this Freddy Krueger like burned face.
That is not, maybe I have slight like little.
It does look like she increased the detail a little bit.
Maybe she used like a sharpening filter.
I wouldn't, there's nothing wrong with this.
I wouldn't,
Okay, I see what she's
All right. Well, what I would say to sweet pea is sweet pea
You know when psyche and I were going back and forth, you know, I
Kind of started what you're running with now
You need to stop because you don't show yourself ever on camera like I know I'm not on camera at this moment
but I'm on camera pretty frequently you never are because you're a coward and
You would never be able to take what you're dishing out and
Psyche is a lot more sensitive than I think a lot of you may realize
as many of us are but
What you're doing is wrong and what's gonna really suck sweet pee is what if somebody were to obtain photos or video footage of your friend?
Miss kitties and really run with it
What if that were to happen?
So I think you should we have it down a bit. Yeah, we have that footage. I mean, it's like we have
Beat is you know cammy up in front of the make I have this one of here
I think you like this one Alexander. I don't know if you've seen this
I do have here's a real-life photo of her
Let me see. Where is this one? Yeah, it's like I think it's for this one. Oh
I might be this one. Oh, there's one
don't know who I don't know what she's expecting well but but there's one more
hold on there's a I think it was the one where she but and where's that I mean I
have I have Sandman's real face too I mean I have well here's Sandman and
Crystal Marie they're playing Eugeo one night and this might be a little too
too flattering and Crystal Marie but we're not Crystal I mean Crystal Anne
there's there's Sandman right there
I just feel like if you're not somebody who's consistently on camera, you don't need to
say anything.
If you are someone who's consistently on camera, you know, maybe you have a leg to
stand on, but, um, right, and they're not prepared to take what you dish out if you
choose to dish it out.
Yeah, because I did I mean I did have a I mean at one point I did have a real picture of sweepy
I don't know if I still have that one. I'm just looking down right now. It's oh my god. There's KZ
well, I just don't like the
There's a certain sort of
attitude that
Doesn't really resonate with me when it comes to some of these groups
And I just kind of feel like they don't really bring anything to the table you have a lot of people saying all this stuff about others but they embody very little talent.
They contribute very little they're just existing to create negative energy.
Right.
I mean there's a lot and that mean that's called you have you heard of loose.
There's something no, what's loose? Loose is like a negative energy that's generated from like me
Maybe people people crash out or something like that and they they feed on this because they feed on the negative energy
And so what I'll try to trigger you and upset you in order to get this negative energy out there
So they can like kind of suck it out like a vampire. Okay. I just I just looked it up
I've never heard that term before it's a medical term for psychic energy or life force
Generated by living beings particularly humans through intense emotional experience
Conspiracy and spiritual theories as a harvested energy, especially pain or fear used by non physical entities or interdimensional beings for sustenance, you know, this is very interesting to me, because as you know, I'm very into aliens, extraterrestrials, interdimensional beings, and there has been a theory for many years that there's a particular
interdimensional and extraterrestrial group. One and the same in this particular case
that does feed off of our heightened emotional experiences and just considering the pattern
of some of these. See this is why I'll tell you I don't think I do think that there are some
disembodied beings that are a part of these communities and I think that's why we never
Who's to say that the internet hasn't become something to wear?
It's tapping into another reality to where a part of the reason that we don't see certain people is because they're not people
I've thought this for a while. I could be wrong, but I
What is it? It's a call that they live there's a movie called they live where they had this I know that movie
Yeah, yeah. Oh, I think I might be able to find I think I did get like a picture of sweepie
I mean, I think I did see her one time like the real sweepie. I'm gonna see if I have this picture of right
I know it's I think it's I think it's right around here and I did leave a few things. Yeah. Okay. Oh, yeah
I found her right here. So this is the reals. This is the actual base on the real the real sweet pea
This is the picture guys and you know, no shade, you know
This is the real sweet pea
Here you go. So it's I
Wonder why she never cams up. Let me get the whole thing. There we go. There. Can we see it like that?
Yeah, I see it. Okay
Yeah
Well, that's I I mean, I don't know who she is
I don't care at this point because I just kind of feel like when it comes to that number one
You are not balding. Okay. You have a beautiful head of hair. Thank you a lot of people are very jealous of
Shiny it looks healthy. It's a nice texture
Desperately make me Syrax and it's like I'm not Syrax. I don't have these like these sores on my head or with spider bites
Or whatever he has on his head. He has some kind of like scabbing or something like that. I don't have that
I'm even balding. I'm not retarded like Syrax. You're actually as I was saying before this over this past month
I think that you're looking healthier not that you were looking unhealthy before but I just feel like
You know for those who don't know psyche did deal with the loss not too long ago
Not too dissimilar to myself and when you go through that kind of a loss it does affect you physically
I'm just now bouncing back to where I was and you're bouncing back to yeah
And some of you out there who haven't gone through certain forms of losses
May God help you when you do
considering how
Lacking empathy some of you
Yeah are just saying
Yeah, I mean some of the picture maybe didn't look like my dad when he was like nine almost 90 years old
You know, but maybe the skin but that's like, you know, I have another 50 years to go to that
And so or you know, if you're another 40 years and maybe more than 50
I mean you you need to give yourself some credit because you you
You do like your drinks just as I do you do like your cigars, but that's not determination as to how long you live a
Lot of it does have to do with the energy that you choose to accept or reject and also that you emit
Right and look at 49 people right now. So that's like not much of a boycott on their part, you know
I do like you know, there are not focusing on that. I'm not even I'm not even I'm just like I'm kind of happy like is it's like, you know
I do have people that are talking in the chat and people that are and it's whatever
It's like, you know, Tommy James badmouthing me and
Well, look at how much he's badmouthed me as good as I was to him. I mean he really you know
Look at this point. He can barely walk
That's karma, okay
Look it's all that bad energy that he emits and that he's a part of I mean we're seeing him basically
Deterior rate. I mean he's supposed to be in his 30s. He's already looking like he's in his mid 40s
Honestly, I mean talk about balding. You want to talk about really balding trying to cover it up with the comb over
He his feet are fucked up. He can barely walk. He's severely overweight. Now that is the actual locale
Right, and I don't think I'm okay. It's like a you're not a locale
No, but see these the reason that some of these people are coming at you so aggressively is because they don't want to be defined as
Or maybe I should call them loose cows because that's what they are like vampire
They're so for it. They're so afraid that people are gonna notice in mass that they're the actual
gross ones, I'll just call it that the gross ones,
cause they are, it ain't you.
They're just deflecting.
And that's why like so little of them will even attack you
really like because they want you around.
They want you there so they can buy.
Well, they want to be attached to you too,
because you're doing something special that they cannot do.
Right. And it's like, and it's like, they don't,
maybe they don't recognize that or they, or they,
I think they probably.
Oh, they recognize it.
They're jealous.
Okay.
Yeah, I mean they can't cam up their age and like milk in the sun
No talent
No skill no content nothing that they're bringing to the table when they look at you they're looking
You don't have the right mindset yet as far as I think you do but you're not accepting of your own status
Right, but I guess that's why i'm around. Yeah to uh be that snob
Yeah
Yeah, okay. Thank you. Yes. Yes. I'm blessed to stop worrying about thank you
These you know, they're they're loose losers looshers. Yeah loose cows. Yes
Yes, and yes, and that's what they're after. They're after a reaction. They're like, oh, let's trigger him
Let's do this. Let's here's how we can mess with them next and it's like you're not really messing with me
I've already been through like I was trained in psychological warfare by a Russian, you know
It doesn't really get much better than that, you know, my best friend since 2008
Is it was Russian, you know and and he's put me through the MK ultra and it's put me in it's like I've been through all I've been
I understand mind control and all this.
I don't use it on people because it's like,
but I do know when it's being used on me
and I see this manipulation that they're using,
because I haven't been through anything,
even just being born gay or,
it's like you're gonna be bullied throughout your life
for showing any kind of feminine trait
or sensitivity or anything that it's like,
anybody else is like, it's very excuse, I think, but.
I know it's just when it comes to me, it's like, you know, we're the scapegoats. Capricorns are scapegoats
We are the we are the devil and the tarot
And so it's very easy to project because we have the material world that we were basically in our hands
This is our world. Basically. We're the rulers of the world think the first
God was the Capricorn Enki the Enki and Mesopotamian mythology was the Capricorn
That's where the goat came from if you research the origin of Capricorn
You know that was the first well also um there's a goat is an acronym for greatest of all time
Yes, right and it's like and we and also this it's a sign of the father
It's um the sign of the mason
It's um
And so natural masons any capricorn is basically a free mason without having to even like you know
Go through the porch mason
Steps of it. They're already ahead of it. It's like that's why masons are afraid to do birthday charts a lot of the times is because
they see exactly what's going on and so they're not gonna want to see some certain things like
if they were to examine my birthday and your birthday and things like that we would oh yeah
sure okay Zia's brother yeah sure exactly
Well, then that's why Alistair Crowley, when he had a poem that gave away one of the biggest Masonic secrets,
I think the poem was called something about sucking eggs or something like that,
but he wrote a poem about it and he was contacted and he went right above the 33rd degree just by knowing that knowledge.
And so, yes, I understand how some of it works and stuff, because I am in the natural Mason too.
It's like the builders, the architects, and we build things, Alex, we build channels.
We do build things yes, and that's where the jealousy comes in because when you build something
You control a lot
Right and they want to be the managers of urban managers and the and the you know
Different admins and the plumbers and all these different things
And as I i'm going to read to you my little um proclamation that I had to post the other day because every once in a while I have to um
Tell people what's really up
So I'm just going to read this real quick. I posted this two days ago on my IRL news time channel
To those of you within attached to or who simply observe these IRL live streaming communities who
Believe that you can dictate or demand a thing from me. You're sadly mistaken
I don't owe these communities a damn thing.
If anything, these communities owe me in a major way.
Over the years, my presence in these communities legitimized many.
I contributed as a chatter, live streamer, panel guest, commentator, recapper, and website
developer.
I put up with more BS within these communities than my peers, more hate, more attacks, and
more legally actionable slander slash defamation.
Most of it stemming from you, the viewers, being racist extremists.
So I can't relate to the LGBTQ thing so much, but hey, I'm a black woman, which is something
I can never hide.
I've also donated to streamers more so than the majority of viewers.
In addition, I do not request donations or even accept donations for the most part, being
that I don't need them nor do I like anyone believing I'm beholden to them.
Considering the aforementioned, I'd suggest that those of you accustomed to unjustly
bossing others around to stay the fuck away from me.
If you don't like the content of my channels, don't watch.
And I've made it clear that I want zero communication with it. I'm sorry
And if I've made it clear, I want zero communication with you accept it. So that was just my rant
But I put those out every now and then
just because
Sometimes people need a reality check from the goats
Right. Is that how good sound right? Yeah. Yeah, I've seen a lot of goats strangely like in my everyday life
I was running some errands yesterday, and I passed at least
three
billboards or you know just some sort of pictures of goats so I think that the
energy of existence is reminding me a little bit of that.
Or maybe I'm just more focused on that. I don't know and also goats and there's you know goats
You know, they can climb trees they can scream they can faint they can escape from all kinds of situations
They're like little escape artists. What Capricorn is from the word escape, you know
CAP like, you know capers or escape like we're gonna keep bringing we're good at this I didn't know that okay
That's good to know we're capricious also
If you look up, like there's something called star, star symbolism or something like that, and look up the Capricorn constellation and like there's all the mythology associated with Capricorn, Capricorn is associated with Enki, like the god of the sweet waters, the god of magic, the god of Sumerian, ancient Sumeria, where they just had the clay tablets, he was the god of creation, he saved Inanna from the underworld, he created these.
transgender beings by the dirt under his fingernails. He did the DNA and he created these transgender
beings to go down to the queen of hell. It's a great story. I can show you. Well, it might be
more than a story. I mean, how do we know that, okay, you have all these classifications of different
types of people, you know, but how do we know that we're just reclassifying what's always been?
but that we don't acknowledge us being a part of something that we don't acknowledge as reality.
Right exactly. I mean, it's like this is basically a dream. It's just basically like a very realistic dream
That keeps lasting and lasting and lasting
But you think like when we even when we go to sleep in dream we stop dreaming we have dreams within dreams within dreams
Like we can be a dream of our soul, you know, and like a really
Realistic long one, but just to teach us the certain lessons we need to learn here, you know, and it's like even like
Even like death is the release from this earthly body
so there's nothing to get into the earthly body that you cannot escape from right and so
And then there's a soul continue like this energy cannot be created or destroyed is like what they say, right?
Well, some people believe that we never really die that there's you know infinite
Versions of us. It's like a multiverse theory. I'm not sure if I'm gonna explain it correctly
but to where our consciousness goes to
What's what's most conducive to our being over and over with every choice we make that that could be?
Right, I mean that and that is like actually like it makes sense not to my like my mind necessarily
It makes sense to like my spirit my soul like I feel this
I feel this like my soul. I'm gonna use my moderation powers. I know I shouldn't
I'm gonna do it hold on we log into my moderator account because
But the loosh the loosh is trying to do something and I don't like it. I
feel like this if you
Don't like what you're hearing
Get the hell out
Exactly, you know, I have a few clever if you live a little bit of this if you want to check it out
This is you need to tear everything down to build something new
Like you have to walk away from everything you've built
Not because you're lost, but because something else is calling you.
There's an ancient story for that, one of the oldest we have, and it's about a goddess
who did exactly that.
This is the story of Anama and her journey to the underworld.
From the great above, she aimed her attention at the great below, and Ana, the Queen of
Heaven, master of cities and temples, decided to leave it all behind.
She was answering a call from the deepest, darkest part of existence.
She gathered her seven divine powers, symbols of her authority and war.
She put on her crown, arranged her hair with intention, and adorned herself with jewels.
She wore a garment of ladyship and helped the measuring rod and mine.
The very tools used to shape reality. She was dressed for power.
Before she left, she gave instructions to her loyal attendant, Mancobora.
I'm going down, she said, calm and direct.
If I don't return in three days, you must become my voice.
You will mourn for me, beat the drums in the abandoned temples, and knock on the doors of the gods until they listen.
She was clear if the high gods refuse go to Enki. He understands the secret of revival
He knows how to cheat death and with that and Anna descended
She arrived at the gates of the underworld
The land of no return and banged on the door like she owned the place open up. Nettie. I'm here
Nettie the gatekeeper was skeptical. Why would you queen of heaven choose a road that never gives back what it takes?
Anana had a cover story ready.
She was there, she said, for the funeral of her sister's husband.
Nettie delivered the message to his queen, Irek Kikala, ruler of the underworld.
When Irek Kikala heard her sister had arrived, dressed in all her finery and armed with divine
powers, she wasn't happy.
She then gave a command that followed the one unbreakable law of the underworld.
Both the seven dates, she told Mehdi, open them one by one, and at each gate you will
take something from her, strip her of her power, remove her claims to authority.
So the ritual began.
At the first gate, Mehdi took Inona's crown.
Why are you doing this?
She demanded.
The laws of the underworld must be fulfilled. Do not question them.
At the second gate, they took the lappist beads from her throat.
At the third, the beads from her chest.
Gate by gate, she was stripped of her power, her symbols, her identity.
Her ring, her measuring tools, and finally, at the seventh and final gate, her garment of ladyship.
By the time she entered the throne room, she was no longer Anana the decorated, the powerful, the famous.
She was just Anana.
And what did she do?
She walked straight to her sister's throne, moved her aside, and sat down herself.
This was the ultimate trespass.
You don't just walk into the underworld and claim it's throne.
With seven judges of the underworld, the Anana turned their gaze upon her.
It was a gaze that ends stories.
Their voices condemned her, and their judgment fell upon her like a physical weight.
Anana was reduced.
Not killed in a fight, but unmade.
Her essence was undone, and her lifeless body was hung on a hook.
Three days and three nights passed.
She mourned, beat the drum, and went from god to god, pleading for help.
The great gods Enmal and Nanna refused.
No logic was cold, but fair.
She chose to go to the underworld.
She wanted its power, so she must face its consequences.
The underworld always claims its own.
So Ninkubara went to Enki, the god of wisdom and magic,
the one who knows the cheat codes of reality.
When Enki heard what had happened, his heart sank.
What has my daughter done?
He cried.
From the dirt under his fingernails, he created two tiny, clever beings.
He gave them a plant and water of life and a very specific mission.
Slip into the underworld like flies, he instructed.
Find my niece, Iraki Kala.
She will be in great pain.
Do not lecture her.
Do not try to fix her.
Just mirror her suffering. When she groans, you groan with her.
The two small beings did exactly that.
They found Eric Kyla, not as a queen on a throne,
but as a being in raw, per the agony.
And as she cried out in pain, they echoed her cries.
They didn't offer solutions, they offered empathy.
They validated her suffering.
Moved by this unexpected compassion, Iriki Gala offered them a reward, anything they wanted.
A river, a field, a mountain of green. They refused it all.
Just give us the body hanging on the hook, they said.
That is your queen, Iriki Gala warned.
Whether it is our queen or our king, they replied. Give it to us. She agreed.
They took Inanna's body, used the plant and water of life, and Inanna rose again.
But resurrection always comes with the receipt.
The underworld does not simply lose inventory.
The judges declared, if Inanna is to return to the world above, she must provide a substitute.
So Inanna ascended, but not a well.
She was escorted by the gala, relentless demons who collect the debts of the underworld.
They first came to the loyal Mancubora, still dressed in mourning, a demon's motion to
take her.
No, Anana commanded, not her.
She followed my instructions.
She did not abandon me.
They moved on to others who had mourned her, and each time, Anana protected them.
Finally, they arrived at an apple grove, and there sat her husband, Demusid.
He was dressed in magnificent clothes, sitting on a magnificent throne,
looking completely untouched by the cosmic drama, but had just unfolded.
He hadn't mourned. He hadn't noticed she was gone.
He was just dot, dot, dot, enjoying his status.
And on his gaze turned to ice. Her voice became a verdict.
Take him. The demon seized-
Yeah, take him!
And though he cried out and tried to escape, his fate was sealed.
The story doesn't end with a clean happily ever after, it ends with a cosmic compromise,
a cycle.
For half the year, Demzit descends to the underworld.
For the other half, his sister takes his place.
The price is always paid, the balance is always kept.
This isn't just an old story.
It's a blueprint for transformation.
An honest dissent wasn't a punishment, it was a choice, it was a deliberate initiation.
She walked into the one place her power and status meant nothing
To confront the parts of reality you can't negotiate with the seven gates where she was stripped of her powers
Represent a process of ego death
Think about what was taken her crown of authority her symbols of desirability
Her tools for controlling reality by the end. She wasn't a brand or a persona. She was just a being
This is what it looks like when life strips away your coping mechanisms, one by one, until you have to meet your true self.
Her real crime wasn't visiting. It was trying to take over.
When she sat on her sister's throne, she trespassed on a domain that wasn't hers.
The myth is clear. You can visit the shadow, but you can't colonize it.
You can't control it with your old rules and the rescue.
It's one of the most profound psychological insights ever written.
The underworld wasn't conquered by force.
It was moved by empathy, and Keith didn't send an army.
He sent two tiny beings who simply mirrored Irak Kigala's pain.
They showed us that deep suffering doesn't respond to advice or lectures, it responds
to being seen and validated.
Finally, the substitute.
This is the core law of transformation.
You can't gain something new without letting something old go.
There's always a cost.
And why was Demusa chosen?
Because he was the one who was complacent.
He was the part of Anana's life that was out of sync with her transformation,
the part that refused to change.
The myth tells us a brutal truth.
If you go through a profound change,
the parts of your life that refuse to change with you
may not survive the journey.
If you don't consciously choose what to sacrifice for your growth,
the universe will choose for you.
So the story of Anana isn't just about a goddess.
It's about the cyclical nature of life, death, and rebirth.
It is a map for anyone who has ever had to descend into their own darkness to find a
new kind of light.
It reminds us that transformation is costly, that empathy is a superpower, and that sometimes
you have to be stripped of everything to find out who you truly are.
Thank you so much for joining me on this journey into one of humanity's oldest stories.
I like that story. It actually reminds me a little bit of the Persephone story. Yes
It's similar not not exactly, but it's very similar also very true right
Or a piece of sense into the underworld as well to get his his love your I guess her name was
Euro dicey. Yeah, Euro dicey and they said, okay
Well, you can he had such beautiful music. They all allowed him and their hearts were changed
But then they said you can't look back and make sure you have to like just have faith
that she's behind you.
And at the last minute,
when he dressed when he was coming to the overworld,
he turned around and looked at her
and then she was dragged back to the underworld
because he didn't have the faith.
And so that's also,
and then he was eventually torn apart by the Mayanids
and his head continued giving prophecies
that turned to the Baphomet.
Interesting things like that.
You know, there's a lot of connections in the cult
that can be made.
And with a lot of interesting things,
that's why I say study the occult.
But it is a journey, you know, I'm just naturally well, you have to be ready to you
You know, I was saying on one of my recent lives that
And and I guess I can't say I've known you a long time, but I've known you for a while now
What I really like about you is that at no point in time. Have you ever?
Attempted to influence me spiritually in any direction. I
like that
I really like that about you because sometimes you can find yourself out of balance if you
don't explore other spiritual paths or at least if you don't at least acquaint yourself
with those paths.
And what I like about that story is that it does present.
the underworld or what's perceived as the underworld and
You do have to know about the darkness
Just as you know about the light or you you won't have a complete picture of much of anything including yourself
Right and who you are sometimes you have to embrace the darkness in order to really appreciate the light
but
Everybody's shadow work and everyone I think in this world is like oh
of them have individual shadows that can be, that need chasing, right, and it's like that, that work can only be done by each of them going through their, facing their personal shadow, not projecting onto the capricorn or the goat, or whatever, whatever they, whatever they do, um, you know, and I'll find something, I'll find like the
The best of the goats or something like that. I need to find the best of the goats video like you know because they can scream
They can like you know jump over fences
With the Capricorns escape escape artists, you know
these
Mountains that are like me that are like a sheer rock cliff
Yeah, I was really surprised when you showed me that video because that was almost a
90 degree vertical incline. It was pretty close to it and those goats
But their hooves the way their hooves are is interesting if you look at
How they're little that they're able to
Kind of grab on to things with their little hooves
This is a little bit if you don't mind. This is like about the goats. Yeah, if you can yeah
This is best of the this is why go to the funniest animals. Yeah, check this out
They are funny the way that they behave and they're cute too
Nobody's gonna know
This little goat be like we're in the same size, so the same family
From farmyard to dojo, he's unleashing the inner kung fu master
I'll walk out buddies a lifesaver, they'll keep you fit and even braver.
This little black hole is turning milk into cuteness, isn't it?
Look at this little tail going
Who knew the toughest opponent would be filled with hot air
The next Jurassic Park movie here it comes
You can't sleep in the food bowl, Gary. I need to feed you
Gary
Come to Go Fattery the gym where you might not only can get fit but also fun
How I imagine myself when I'm becoming an auntie
This must be tasting like dreams and unicorns, huh?
of our Mondays. Stay away from me a good morning your room service right there outside today
When you're deep on your phone and dad walks in.
They really like people.
They do. Prove that God is also a clean dog.
No doubt they're walking the runway. Can you spot the real trendsetter?
Me when my human forgets to refill the air
It's so cute how they just bounce around.
Just get it!
They're like, hold up!
Move my little fluffy balls to our party.
Some people do have the mess pet.
I would!
Welcome to our masterclass in branch eating.
Enroll the whole family for a free demo.
You gotta have a yard if you're gonna have one.
How I picture myself on the weekend
Today
Number what are a little human like especially when they have the little beard yeah
The reason why people call CR7 the go.
Me trying to stay professional at a meeting.
Nah, forget it.
Karaoke at the farm is a whole different game.
When the interviewer asked me why he should hire me.
Come on!
Come...
Baby...
You're trying to focus on one thing, but your brain is a pinball machine.
Come here again.
I think they should buy the goats a trampoline instead.
They're smart. You know, you can tell they're like really...
When somebody mentioned princess in the house...
A couple red bulls. Have you ever had a red bull?
I never had a red bull before, but I had a red bull last night.
I really like red bull.
I got a new necklace. It blows in the dark.
I can't even see it right now. I should do this.
This goat thinks he's a canine unit. Anyone lost the ball?
Thumbs up for this soundtrack.
Sly Chang is the ultimate friendship test. Don't fail.
That's so cute. That's so cute. You know, while we were looking at that, I looked up
Intellect of Goats just because I was curious. It says, Goats possess high intelligence. I thought,
so you can tell by how they behave.
an excellent long-term memory often outperforming other livestock and problem solving and spatial
awareness tasks. They are fast learners capable of solving complex multi-step puzzles such as
operating levers and remembering these skills for up to 10 months. They also have strong social
intelligence recognizing individual humans and animals that's that's neat to know so
You know, don't eat goats. They're smart, but I gotta get going. I gotta get going. Hey, thank you so much for coming on and
You know, and I'm gonna check out. I think maybe you'll do a review of the cold codex. I will okay
Yeah, and also check out Brandon Brandon Q's interview tomorrow 2 p.m. On IRL news time
Yes, yes, you got goat memory. You have long-term memory. You remember
All right, I love you too. Have a great day. Have a great stream also. Goodbye chat. Have a good one. Bye. Bye. Love you
Okay guys, here's the link again, if anyone wants to link.
I mean, I did start drinking a little bit.
I had a hit of the vape,
but I think I'm maintaining pretty good.
But that was funny, you know,
there was some funny stuff there.
I can put on, since I'm a little drunk,
I might just put on like a,
I don't want to fall asleep during it.
I just have to do the individual thing,
but it's like that packy of stuff up.
I mean, I'll do a rumble clip.
Let me see, let me see how I sound rumble.
See what trip kick has he has a new psyche video because he seems to love me
And if I fall asleep during this, I'm sorry, but it'll just be a trip kick for a little bit
Kk versus Sam and let me see all of you all the videos. Let me see
Canadian kick streamer gets triggered. Let me see videos. Okay. There's a Tommy James salmon and Kk versus Tommy on psyches panel
That was recently Q45 versus salmon and psyche away. That was a good one. Let's play this one
I'm eating like some ramen. I guess in this video
I'm gonna I might fall asleep because I've now been drinking I had a freaking I had a drink but
What do you got this it yeah?
Okay, you guys see it here enjoy it okay, Tripp cake shout out
All those houses
He didn't need to do a damn thing
He just stood his ground and laughed at him and he chipped out and ran circles around himself
and ended up walking himself down in the even panel
It was hilarious
Got him so mad that he was fucking, he started talking about dangerous kids
Yeah, yeah, yes
Not even dangerous kids, Maddie's kids
Yup, bad
Oh, Mr. I don't talk about kids. Oh, we don't talk about kids
We'll talk about kids then you're then you're sitting there talking about Maddie's children being mixed race
I know it's it's it's
You call this like over a year ago you said people are gonna start to see through it
It's gonna become a fucking running joke, and that's all it is
That's obvious. It was like a year ago. It's just getting worse now. Yeah. Yeah, I know it's Larry's
His head keeps getting bigger and I can wear
Is it Saturday or Sunday?
I
Chat goes like oh shit here. We go again here goes this motherfucker if I ever get to that point where everybody's just so exhausted of you
Like maybe you should take a break
Now he's in the chat now acting like he wasn't watching the earth the whole time. That's all this nigga does is watch
That's all this nigga does is watch the stream and play Yu-Gi-Oh cards
And didn't we cook to my nigga? Oh my god
My mid you got cooked by DZ easy
I love it, dude. I'm watching this guy.
All that dude does is talk about cooking,
but he says like the same four or five phrases in a row.
How is that cooking? Please, tell me.
You're not educated enough or well-spoken enough
to cook anybody. Let's just be honest here.
you're not witty enough you literally just sit there and cry about shit that
happened three years ago for everybody same thing that you do with big T same
thing that you do with me just well but you did this in 2023 you spit in the
girls hair yeah more bitch happy Easter
I wish that was your mother's hair that I spit in
I
Put a real Easter folks like actual real contact shout out
Tomorrow is Easter weekend
Yeah, so this nigga keeps trying to this this nigga keeps trying to bring up my job because I'm a door-to-door salesman
Like that's supposed to be embarrassing first of all you don't have a job second of all
Everybody may everybody hate on me and made fun of me when I didn't have a job now that I do have a job now
The job's not good enough right now the job's not good enough now now we're gonna make fun of me for having a job great
That makes a ton of sense
No, nigga, nobody even knows what you do. You're probably a security guard. You probably sit on your fat fucking ass all day
Yeah, why are you so fucking fat? Why haven't you gotten any ass in like three years?
When is the last time you felt the
Yes, I know on that caraballo pack. I'm lying. Yes, or no, you know, I could just I could just
Why do you not have a girl
You don't have a woman
You don't have a woman a woman doesn't even know what you smell like because they won't even go near you
I don't smell like fuck out of here. You can't why you can't just a minute. Why bother told everybody smell like shit
Why are you fucking fat and Puerto Rican?
Easy
Yo, this ain't even denying it, bro.
You smell like shit, and your girl told everybody
you smell like shit, nigga.
Denying it.
Love.
You can't deny it.
Come on, bubba.
Sad man, sad man.
The man with no means to blame.
Deep sea cookie, my nigga.
Yeah, he cooked me so much. Yeah, Papa. He cooked you
Look you quiet now
I don't. I don't. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know.
That's all you do is fucking cry. Every fucking day you're on panels crying. Literally driven days out of the week you're on panels fucking crying.
That's all you do is cry about other men on panels. That is your entire fucking existence. That's all you do is cry about other men.
Oh man, this man said this. Oh man, this man said that.
You're a f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f***ing f
Devo a do-boy
I don't go to door to door
With you
I heard a story about Sam man.
I need to be fucking kids.
Tra-ra-ra!
Yeah, Sam man definitely fucks kids.
Sam man definitely fucks kids.
I mean if we can all say lies about each other like I mean we can just we can just say whatever
you know what thank you thank you because you notice how the the panel is so much different
when certain people are on and off right as soon as some people join it just creates this
fucking world and then everybody's arguing yeah every nice time because a fucking fruit
No, don't fuck him. He wants attention. He wants to get he wants to sit up on fucking other people's streams
So that he can click this shit and recap it on his own stream. So he has something to fucking talk about
That's all he does
And you people fucking
Fucking and always the shit out of me
I agree sleep, but you know his fucking game. Why even feed into it? Fuck him
You're right. I feel yeah
It's not like we weren't chilling having a completely normal coffee today
I'm going to show you how to do the Japanese natural osempic. No fluff. Let's get straight to it
They tried to silence me
So now I'm going to teach you the recipe that mimics the effects of the magic pens without the side effects
These ingredients when combined create an effect ten times more powerful than the manjaro shot and like I said
no side effects, because it's 100% natural and you can make it right in your own kitchen.
When I say 10 times more powerful, I mean it. If taken the right way,
this recipe can help any woman over 35 lose so much weight, it'll look like she had cosmetic surgery.
But thanks to the Japanese manjaro trick, my students don't have to hide under baggy
clothes anymore or feel guilty when they go out to dinner with their husbands.
All they do is drink this recipe every morning and the weight just keeps melting off.
One of them started in February and never gained the weight back.
No yo-yo effect, no loose skin, no tired worn-out look.
Honestly, I know a lot of women would pay thousands to learn this.
Pay close attention.
If this video showed up for you, congrats, you got lucky.
For the next two minutes, only I'm releasing a step-by-step video with all the ingredients
and how to make it.
To watch it now, just click the button below this video where it says, Learn More.
Promise me you'll follow the exact amounts and be careful, like the experts recommend,
so you don't end up losing too much weight.
Okay, click the button below to copy the recipe and start feeling your pants loosen
This is the secret to having the kind of body
that'll make other women jealous in 2025.
Go ahead, click the Learn More button.
And don't forget to come send me your before and after pics.
All right, see you soon.
Click anywhere on this video where it says Learn More
to copy the full recipe and make it at home.
What is working in exactly Tommy exactly?
Just having a fucking completely casual normal conversation about nothing and then faggot has to come in here and fucking
Like shut up nobody cares it's like fucking it's early as hell in the morning on the west coast shut up
I say bring him back, but that's just me.
I understand.
Oh, fuck him.
It's like, maybe like a little bit of like back and forth is funny, but then it's getting
to a little too much.
Bro, that's just the entire life is going back and forth.
You guys, you want to raise your hand back because it's like a dollar a minute.
they want to back up such a little hoe
Sam and it's like actually $5 a minute
maybe if you maybe say Sam and maybe if you were like semi likable
people could like tolerate it but like you're fucking and stuff
for a little bit nobody fucking like I know
is really bad and sufferable and that fucking it's terrible
dude and then more time goes on the worst that it gets
No, I mean at least good times has like some sort of comedic value and you can't really take them too seriously
But this dude's same man just gets online and cries about everybody all day long
Just like do you ever get fucking tired of it? Do you ever get tired of fucking crying?
Do you ever get tired of not getting any pussy? Do you ever get tired of playing with Yu-Gi-Oh cards and playing Roblox?
I could not be me, bro.
Damn
Not my life. I could don't never fucking get up enough of it. He just cries all day long
There's not three people that like him there's three people that utilize him because they know it's beneficial to them
Isn't anybody that likes him he has people he has people that that know that he's useful. He's a useful idiot. That's what he is
Yeah, they're called
Useful it or communism or something useful idiots. That's what he is. He's a useful fucking idiot
Whatever anybody says
Never go against any grain
I'd love to see you in real life same man, I would smack the literal shit out of you
I'd love to see that, dude. I'd love it!
I
Know what the real word is based on he fell asleep winning those noodles and then you're gonna try to get some of those noodles
Yeah, these are the best
Talking shit to KK you understand that KK literally exposed the shit out of you and that
Stay man. Stay man. You're really gonna talk to talk to KK like that
It's him faking an interaction with her
like little details like I grabbed your butt and picked it up in Mercedes or whatever and it was
all that dude is a weirdo all the f***ing lie
Why anybody believes anything this guy says after that is beyond fucking me after making a homo script like that
Well, he tried this while I've been seen with not one two three
multiple women on straight
But you claim all this bullshit is constantly talking about you dick. Why don't you get fucked?
Go die.
I'll get a hook.
Isn't that what's disgusting way to say dick?
Why don't you go die slow?
Oh my god.
Whoops.
They can't say you smell like shit cuz you never met her. You've never been with a woman before
She definitely told us how you you have to be with a woman in order for them to say that you smell like shit
How grubby you are and how multiple face calls you were seen with the same clothes on
Meaning you don't change your clothes for multiple days. She said she's FaceTime with you every day. She said you're grubby
Dirty tank top on, fucking harem as she told us all about you dude.
I know you, he just looks like a dirty ass nigga.
Yeah
What are we talking about?
He ain't got to put a bed on her wishlist and you're a bum ass nigga. That's my like shit
They can put her bed on the wishlist and it's like shit why are we talking about
Why we're doing so much talking
What's that noise?
Your arms are fucked up.
I don't like the sound.
Is that him?
Yeah, I know.
Is that me?
Nick, are you mad?
You want to protect Psyche?
This is a hug box for you, papa.
Yeah, I think that's the name.
Grab your hook behind the door.
Door to door.
Wow
Bye-bye little black boy
There we go. I knocked the headphones on, brother.
Thank you.
It's like a little chihuahua.
He comes up and goes...
And then you kick him.
You know, Sam, I tell us about people's teeth and stuff like that,
and he's like missing teeth.
I mean...
Oh, I don't want to know what his dental's like after all those years
of being a queer.
I appreciate you letting me on along with my best behavior. No bigotry, no fagotry, no nicotry.
Thank you.
Let me have cakey here. Let me have cakey here. Say hi. I want one second. Let me make sure it's here.